Harold Stein Filk Collection
Harold Stein Filk Archive
- Audio
  - Physical Media
    - Filk, 1980s; 1 copy; Notes: This appears to be disc 1/2 Origin: Random filk MP3s, mostly of a 1980s vintage Convention: NA; genreform: Burnt CD (Box 4)
    - Filk .wavs RAW Michael Longcor - Undead, Heather Alexander, Live, Star Song - Songs for Star Voyagers, 1 copy; Notes: .wavs of the whole albums and also of individual songs Origin: Rips of tapes Convention: NA; genreform: Burnt CD (Box 4)
    - I-Con 26 (2007) Filk Recordings Disc 1 of 2 Brobdingnagian Bards, The FuMP concert, Kenny Young and the Eggplants, Open Filk, Sat Night, Floating Filk Studios; 1 copy; Notes: Origin: Floating Filk Studios Convention: NA; genreform: Burnt CD (Box 4)
    - I-Con 26 (2007) Open Filk (Sat) 3/07 Disc 2 of 2, Floating Filk Studios; 1 copy; Notes: Origin: Floating Filk Studios Convention: NA; genreform: Burnt CD (Box 4)
    - Innocuous looking CD titled ""Travel Filk"", 1 copy; Notes: See full contents in tabe marked Collections; genreform: Burnt CD (Box 1)
    - NYC Housefilk 5/07 MP3s, Faw File, 2008; Floating Filk Studios; 1 copy; Notes: Origin: Floating Filk Studios Convention: NA; genreform: Burnt CD (Box 4)
    - NYC Housefilk 5/07, Edited, Split Files, 1/08, 2008; Floating Filk Studios; 1 copy; Notes: Origin: Floating Filk Studios Convention: NA; genreform: Burnt CD (Box 4)
    - NYC Housefilk 9/08 Disc 1/2, Floating Filk Studios; 1 copy; Notes: Origin: Floating Filk Studios Convention: NA; genreform: Burnt CD (Box 4)
    - NYC Housefilk 9/08 Disc 2/2, Floating Filk Studios; 1 copy; Notes: Origin: Floating Filk Studios Convention: NA; genreform: Burnt CD (Box 4)
    - Philly Housefilk Aug 11, 2007, Disc 1 of 2, Afternoon, Floating Filk Studios; 1 copy; Notes: Origin: Floating Filk Studios Convention: NA; genreform: Burnt CD (Box 4)
    - Philly housefilk, Disc 2 of 2, Aug 11, 2007, Evening, ends at 12:20 am, Floating Filk Studios; 1 copy; Notes: Origin: Floating Filk Studios Convention: NA; genreform: Burnt CD (Box 4)
    - Unlabelled collection of albums, 1 copy; Notes: See full contents in tab marked Collections; genreform: Burnt CD (Box 1)
    - Unlabelled collection of albums, 1 copy; Notes: See full contents in tab marked Collections Origin: -; genreform: Burnt CD (Box 1)
    - Radio Aahs, 1995; 1 copy; Notes: Origin: April 1995 No. 2; genreform: CD (Box 9)
      CD; audio
    - Dr. Demento's 30th Anniversary Collection: Dementia 2000!, Rhino Entertainment Company; 1 copy; Notes: Origin: @2000 Rhino Entertainment Company Convention: NA; genreform: Commercial Box Set (Box 3)
      Convention -- NA; Commercial Box Set; audio
    - Bare Facts, Davis, Bill; 1 copy; Notes: Available on CD Baby Origin:; genreform: Download card (Box 7)
      Download card; audio
    - Live at Arisia, The Subs; 1 copy; Notes: Available on CD Baby Origin:; genreform: Download card (Box 7)
    - Riding Shotgun, Boombox on the Dash, Riding Shotgun; 1 copy; Notes: Origin:; genreform: Download card (Box 7)
    - Sci Fi Drinking Songs, 2012; 1 copy; Notes: Full color, double sided card for CD Baby download Origin:; genreform: Download card (Box 13)
    - Selfie Absorbed - download card, Jacobs, Drew; 1 copy; Notes: Available on CD Baby Origin:; genreform: Download card (Box 7)
    - Stolen Season - SJ Tucker - sticker and download code, 1 copy; Notes: Origin:; genreform: Download card (Box 7)
    - Waterwings, Pinsker, Sarah; 1 copy; Notes: Origin:; genreform: Download card (Box 7)
    - Download code for Earworm, Floating Filk Studios; 1 copy; Notes: Origin: Floating Filk Studios Convention: NA; genreform: Download code (Box 7)
      Download code; audio
    - Earworm download code, reserved for Deb Wunder, 1 copy; Notes: Origin:; genreform: Download code (Box 7)
    - Highlights of Filkcon 2, Floating Filk Studios; 1 copy; Notes: 36wy-ut4f Origin: Floating Filk Studios; genreform: Download code (Box 2)
    - Thanksgiving vs. Christmas the Musical, the commentary, 8 August 2015; 1 copy; Notes: Molly Lewis, et al Origin: 42224; genreform: Download code (Box 7)
    - The Wanderlings Volume 1, Hudson, Leslie; 1 copy; Notes: Download code that looks like a CD insert card Origin: Convention: NA; genreform: Download code (Box 7)
    - Tricky Pixie - Live! Soul Food Books Redmond, WA, Tricky Pixie; 1 copy; Notes: A limited release of Tricky Pixie's first official concert Origin: Full liner notes and track listing at www.trickypixie.com Convention: NA; genreform: Limited Edition CD (Box 6)
      Convention -- NA; CD -- Limited Edition; audio
    - Mini CD with drivers for Alcor media Smart card reader driver, 1 copy; Notes: Origin:; genreform: Mini CD (Box 2)
      Mini CD; audio
    - C6-1, Might be 2006; 1 copy; Notes: Mini - 003 third box of minidiscs #1 Origin:; genreform: MiniDisc (Box 17)
      MiniDisc; audio
    - C6-2, Might be 2006; 1 copy; Notes: Mini - 003 third box of minidiscs #2 Origin:; genreform: MiniDisc (Box 17)
    - C6-3, Might be 2006; 1 copy; Notes: Mini - 003 third box of minidiscs #3 Origin:; genreform: MiniDisc (Box 17)
    - C6-4, Might be 2006; 1 copy; Notes: Mini - 003 third box of minidiscs #4 Origin:; genreform: MiniDisc (Box 17)
    - C6-5, Might be 2006; 1 copy; Notes: Mini - 003 third box of minidiscs #5 Origin:; genreform: MiniDisc (Box 17)
    - C6-7, 2006; 1 copy; Notes: Loose in box - Could be Confluence 2006 based on position in sequence Origin:; genreform: MiniDisc (Box 17)
    - C6-8, 2006; 1 copy; Notes: Loose in box - Could be Confluence 2006 based on position in sequence Origin:; genreform: MiniDisc (Box 17)
    - C6-9, 2006; 1 copy; Notes: Loose in box - Could be Confluence 2006 based on position in sequence Origin:; genreform: MiniDisc (Box 17)
    - GAFia - GF15 | DFS Disc 15 | 07/07/01 Sci-Fi-Summer | 08/18/01 Housefilk | 09/08/01 Housefilk, 2001; 1 copy; Notes: Mini - 009 ninth box of minidiscs #1 Origin:; genreform: MiniDisc (Box 17)
    - GF-17 GaFia disc 17 12/09/01, 02/23/02, 06/14/02, 2002; 1 copy; Notes: Mini - 015 fifteenth box of minidiscs #1 Origin:; genreform: MiniDisc (Box 17)
    - GF-18 GaFia disc 18 Sci Fi Summer June 14-16, 2002, 1 copy; Notes: Mini - 015 fifteenth box of minidiscs #2 Origin:; genreform: MiniDisc (Box 17)
    - GF-19 GaFia disc 19, 1 copy; Notes: Mini - 015 fifteenth box of minidiscs #3 Origin:; genreform: MiniDisc (Box 17)
    - GF-20 GaFia disc 20, 1 copy; Notes: Mini - 015 fifteenth box of minidiscs #4 Origin:; genreform: MiniDisc (Box 17)
    - GF-21 GaFia disc 21, 1 copy; Notes: Mini - 015 fifteenth box of minidiscs #5 Origin:; genreform: MiniDisc (Box 17)
    - Kathy Mar ~60 min Toc error on playback ~2 min (on Sharp), 1 copy; Notes: Mini - 008 eighth box of minidiscs #13 Origin:; genreform: MiniDisc (Box 17)
    - MS-1 Mid-South Con 2007 - Disc 1, 1 copy; Notes: Mini - 010 tenth box of minidiscs #5 NASFilk 2005 - 4 discs / MidSouthCon 2007 2 discs Origin:; genreform: MiniDisc (Box 17)
    - MS-2 Mid South Con 2007 - Disc 2, 1 copy; Notes: Mini - 010 tenth box of minidiscs #6 NASFilk 2005 - 4 discs / MidSouthCon 2007 2 disc Origin:; genreform: MiniDisc (Box 17)
    - NS-1 NASFic 2005-1, 1 copy; Notes: Mini - 010 tenth box of minidiscs #1 NASFilk 2005 - 4 discs / MidSouthCon 2007 2 discs Origin:; genreform: MiniDisc (Box 17)
    - NS-2, 2005; 1 copy; Notes: Mini - 010 tenth box of minidiscs #2 NASFilk 2005 - 4 discs / MidSouthCon 2007 2 discs Origin:; genreform: MiniDisc (Box 17)
    - NS-3, 2005; 1 copy; Notes: Mini - 010 tenth box of minidiscs #3 NASFilk 2005 - 4 discs / MidSouthCon 2007 2 discs Origin:; genreform: MiniDisc (Box 17)
    - NS-4, 2005; 1 copy; Notes: Mini - 010 tenth box of minidiscs #4 NASFilk 2005 - 4 discs / MidSouthCon 2007 2 discs Origin:; genreform: MiniDisc (Box 17)
    - OVFF 01 BKUP 2, 2007; 1 copy; Notes: In slip cover, track list says: 01, 02 No Greater Love 03-10 Trad/Renn Faire, 11. High Frontier 12. Shebeg Shemore 13. - 14. Yogh, Ash + Thorn 15. Slash in the Pan 16. Know It All By Heart 17. What'll I Do 18. RTFM 19. Lisdoon Varna Dulcimer? 20. Guinevere 21. Divinity ReHeat 22. Sedona 23. Greensl. 24. ??? Whitaker Origin:; genreform: MiniDisc (Box 17)
    - Susan Hickey 5 song set Celtic Festival 2005, 1 copy; Notes: Mini - 015 fifteenth box of minidiscs #6 Origin:; genreform: MiniDisc (Box 17)
    - Unlabelled black minidisc in sleeve, 1 copy; Notes: Mini - 008 eighth box of minidiscs #9 Origin:; genreform: MiniDisc (Box 17)
    - Unlabelled black minidisc in sleeve, 1 copy; Notes: Mini - 008 eighth box of minidiscs #10 Origin:; genreform: MiniDisc (Box 17)
    - Unlabelled yellow minidisc, 1 copy; Notes: Mini - 008 eighth box of minidiscs 5 Origin:; genreform: MiniDisc (Box 17)
    - Unlabelled yellow minidisc, 1 copy; Notes: Mini - 008 eighth box of minidiscs #6 Origin:; genreform: MiniDisc (Box 17)
    - Unlabelled yellow minidisc, 1 copy; Notes: Mini - 008 eighth box of minidiscs #7 Origin:; genreform: MiniDisc (Box 17)
    - Sony MZ-R55 Portable Minidisc Recorder, 1 copy; Notes: Has power supply and microphone and carry bag Origin:; genreform: MiniDisc Player (Box 17)
      MiniDisc Player; audio
    - Third Thymes the Charm, Three Weird Sisters; 1 copy; Notes: Origin:; genreform: Pre-distribution card (Box 7)
      Pre-distribution card; audio
    - Pre-release for Plaid & Personal, 2003; Ghost of a Rose; 1 copy; Notes: Origin: Promotional CD Convention: NA; genreform: Pre-release CD (Box 5)
      Convention -- NA; CD -- Pre-release; audio
    - Printout of Download codes for A Song of Sherwood, Floating Filk Studios; 1 copy; Notes: There are a lot of codes on the sheet. As of 11-28-2019, they are still working Origin: Floating Filk Studios; genreform: Printout of Download codes for A Song of Sherwood (Box 2)
      Printout of Download codes for A Song of Sherwood; audio
    - The Bawdy Ladies' Book: Songs of Love and Lust from a Female Perspective sung by Wild Rose Anabel Graetz and Anne Goodwin with Linda Lombardi, 1986; 1 copy; Notes: Recorded at the Somerville Media Action Project by Mark Lord, Mixed by Anabel Graetz and Mark Lord Origin:; genreform: Professional Cassette (Box 17)
      Professional Cassette; audio
    - Dragonsongs, Performing Arts Press; 1 copy; Notes: This is a tape of music inspired by Anne McCaffery's Pern novels Origin: Performaing Arts Press; genreform: Professional Cassette (Box 2)
    - Who Let Him In Here?!?, Smith, Tom; Dodeka Records; 1 copy; Notes: This is Tom Smith's widely available commercial filk tape, in good condition. Origin: Dodeka Records; genreform: Professional Cassette (Box 2)
    - Alive and Filking, Rogow, Roberta; Floating Filk Studios; 6 copy; Notes: Origin: Floating Filk Studios; genreform: Professional CD (Box 1)
      CD -- Professional; audio
    - Dark Deeds & Desperate Men (and Women), Rogow, Roberta; Floating Filk Studios; 1 copy; Notes: Origin: Floating Filk Studios; genreform: Professional CD (Box 1)
    - Heroes & Villans (& Some In Between), Rogow, Roberta; Floating Filk Studios; 1 copy; Notes: Origin: Floating Filk Studios; genreform: Professional CD (Box 1)
    - Teri Lee, 1 copy; Notes: Origin:; genreform: Tape (Box 17)
      Tape; audio
    - Unlabelled tape, 1 copy; Notes: Origin:; genreform: Tape (Box 17)
    - Unlabelled tape, 1 copy; Notes: Origin:; genreform: Tape (Box 17)
    - Unlabelled tape, 1 copy; Notes: Origin:; genreform: Tape (Box 17)
    - Unlabelled tape, 1 copy; Notes: No case on tape Origin:; genreform: Tape (Box 17)
    - The Passing of Time | The Good Times | Throwaway World - Lawrence Dean, 1 copy; Notes: Probably Lawrence Dean's folk tapes Origin:; genreform: Tape - obvious copy (Box 17)
      Tape - obvious copy; audio
    - Slight scuffed CD with NEFilk and Interfilk logos on it, but no contents, 2 copy; Notes: There doesn't appear to be anything on the disc, but Harold labelled it, probably so he could burn it at NEFilk on demand.; genreform: Unburnt CD (Box 1)
      CD -- Unburnt; audio
    - Albacon 2008 Rebecca Angel Concert Disc 3/3 10/08, Albacon; Floating Filk Studios; 1 copy; Notes: Origin: Floating Filk Studios Convention: Albacon; genreform: Burnt CD (Box 4)
      Convention -- Albacon; CD -- Burnt
  - Demented!, 2007; Dr. SETI; Microcomm; 1 copy; Notes: (signed To Harold, with thanks - Paul Dr. SETI. Harold's name is underlined in the credits of the album as having recorded tracks 5, 9, 10 and 12 at Philcon 2006). Origin: Copyright @2007 Microcomm Cogan Station PA 17728 Convention: Various including: Conterpoint IV, Consonance 2000, Philcon 2005, Werd in Berlin, 2007; genreform: Commercial CD (Box 3)
    Convention -- Werd in Berlin, 2007; CD -- Commercial; Convention -- NEFilk 11. Conterpoint IV (2001); Convention -- Consonance 2000 (Y2K); Convention -- Philcon 2005
  - A Long Time Gone (CD), Cats Laughing; 1 copy; Notes: ""I first encountred Cats Laughing when I was an awkward fanboy, and I was blown away"" - Neil Gaiman Origin: Cats Laughing Reunion at Minicon 50 Convention: Minicon 50; genreform: Commercial CD (Box 5)
    Convention -- Minicon 50; CD -- Commercial
  - A Long Time Gone (DVD), 2016; Cats Laughing; 1 copy; Notes: Origin: Cats Laughing Reunion at Minicon 50 Convention: Minicon 50; genreform: Commercial DVD (Box 5)
    Convention -- Minicon 50; Commercial DVD
  - Millenicon -6 Tape 1, 1995; 1 copy; Notes: This tape contains music from Millenicon -6 in Dayton, OH on March 24-26, 1995. Extensive liner notes in tape case. Origin: Mark Peters Convention: Millenicon -6: 1995; genreform: Tape (Box 17)
    Convention -- Millenicon -6 (1995); Tape
  - Chris Conway - Live!, 2001; Conway, Chris; A New Day Records; 1 copy; Notes: Origin: @2001 A New Day Records Convention: Recorded at Didgeridouze, 12th UK Filk Convention, Milton Keynes, 4th Feb, 2000, 1, 12, 13 recorded at Conthirteena, 13th UK Filk Convention, Eastbourne, 3rd Feb 2001.; genreform: Commercial CD (Box 3)
    Convention -- Recorded at Didgeridouze, 12th UK Filk Convention, Milton Keynes, 4th Feb, 2000, 1, 12, 13 recorded at Conthirteena, 13th UK Filk Convention, Eastbourne, 3rd Feb 2001.; CD -- Commercial
  - Od-Ditties: A Filk Album by Danny Birt, Recorded Live at RavenCon 2011, Birt, Danny; Chris Mezzolesta; VoiceGuy 1 Communications; 1 copy; Notes: Somnifacient Records Origin: Recorded Live at RavenCon 2011 by Chris Mezzolesta of VoiceGuy 1 Communications Convention: RavenCon 2011; genreform: Commercial CD (Box 6)
    Convention -- RavenCon 2011; CD -- Commercial
  - "SSDWC: Geek Pantheon" CD, 2010; Fortuner, Kimberley; 1 copy; Notes: Kim's card inside the CD case Origin: http://comicbookgoddess.com Convention: Balticon 44: 2010; genreform: Commercial CD (Box 3)
    Convention -- Balticon 44: 2010; CD -- Commercial
  - .wav Filk Phoenix @Contabile 14, Zander Nyrond @Marcon 37, Contabile 14; Marcon 37; 1 copy; Notes: .wavs of concerts Origin: Possibly Mark Peters Convention: Contabile 14 and Marcon 37; genreform: Burnt CD (Box 4)
    Convention -- British Filk Convention. 14, Contabile Fortean (2002); Convention -- Marcon 37; CD -- Burnt
  - Chug-A-Lug Donna, CD, The East Coast BOOKHOUSE BOYS; Angelo Badalamenti; Ivers, Peter; 1 copy; Notes: Origin: All songs written by Angelo Badalamenti, ""in Heaven"" written by Peter Ivers. Convention: David Lynchfest 8/22/09; genreform: Commercial CD (Box 3)
    Convention -- David Lynchfest (2009); CD -- Commercial
  - Kosher 2: Clam Chowder in Concert at DarkoverCon 2005-2012, Clam Chowder; Fleischer, Eric J.; 1 copy; Notes: 2 Disk set: Bob Esty, John Huff, Cliff Lauffer, Kathy Sobansky, Dennis Hertzog are the lineup of Clam Chowder for these performances. Origin: Video Production by Eric J. Fleischer Convention: Darkover 2005-2012; genreform: Commercial DVD (Box 5)
    Convention -- Darkover 2005-2012; Commercial DVD
  - Live at Harmuni, 2001; Sampson, Mich; 1 copy; Notes: Origin: - Convention: Harmuni, the Briitsh Filk Relaxicon, at York University, 24-26 August, 2001; genreform: Commercial CD (Box 3)
    Convention -- Harmuni, the Briitsh Filk Relaxicon, at York University, 24-26 August, 2001; CD -- Commercial
- Lyrics and Sheet Music
  Song lyrics; Sheet Music
  - Binder/personal collections
    - Personal collection of songs from Lois Welling, About 30 pages of songs in a hole punch metal tab binder with a yellow-orange cover; About 30 sheets in 1 binder; genreform: Personal collection (Box 14)
      Personal collection; Song
    - Binder of Philk Fee-Nom-Ee-Non, 1 copy; Black cover, Philk Fee-Nom-Ee-Non 14-44; genreform: Binder (Black Crate)
      Binder; Zine -- Philk Fee-Nom-Ee-Non
    - Binder of Xenofilkia, 1 copy; Black cover, spine says Xeno 43, contains Xenofilkia 43-65; genreform: Binder (Black Crate)
      Binder; Zine -- Xenofilkia
    - Filk Index Binder - White, 1 copy; White cover, three ring binder, with Filk Index written on the spine, appears to index other binders in our collection. Includes index to tapes and to songs in other binders.; genreform: Binder (Box 12)
      Binder; Index
    - Indexed binder 2673 - 2822, 1 copy; White cover, 2673 is written on spine. Un-numbered (possible duplicates in back of binder); genreform: Binder (Box 12)
      Binder
    - Savitsky Loose Filk Binder, 1 copy; Black cover, contains, alphabetized filk pages - This has been moved to Box #12 for space reasons; genreform: Binder (Box 12)
      Binder; Personal collection
    - Savitsky Misc. Songbooks, 1 copy; White binder with Savitsky, misc filkbooks on the spine; genreform: Binder (Box 12)
      Scope and Contents
      Contents
      Bayfilk
      ConChord
      Philk Fee-Nom-Ee-Non
      Generic songbook
      Kushyon's Flute
      Songs by Keridwen or Mynydd Gwyrdd
      Obnoxious Little Ditties
      The I Hate to Filk Book
      HOPSFA Hymnal
      Filksong Manual
      Swapped Out Songs
      CPSC Songsheet
      The Darkover Songbook
      Binder; Personal collection; Zine -- Philk Fee-Nom-Ee-Non; Bayfilk; Convention -- ConChord; Songbook -- Generic; Kushyon's Flute; Songs by Keridwen or Mynydd Gwyrdd; Obnoxious Little Ditties; The I Hate to Filk Book; HOPSFA Hymnal; Filksong Manual; Swapped Out Songs; CPSC Songsheet; The Darkover Songbook
    - Unlabelled black binder of filk songbooks, 1 binder; Black cover, unlabelled, contains Pernsongs, Rec Room Rhymes Omnibus, More Rec Room Rhymes, Kantele, Anakareon, ConChord and Stone Hill Filk songbooks; genreform: Binder (Black Crate)
      Binder; Songbook; Personal collection; Pernsongs; Rec Room Rhymes Omnibus; More Rec Room Rhymes; Kantele; Anakareon; Convention -- ConChord; Stone Hill Filk songbooks
    - Indexed binder 1301-2000, 1 binder; Black cover, 1301-2000 written on the spine; genreform: Binder (Box 12)
    - Indexed binder 2001-2672, 1 binder; Green cover, 2001-2672 written on spine; genreform: Binder (Box 12)
  - Songbooks
    - Baxter's Complete Beginning Folk Guitar Manuel, 1 copy; Notes: Incomplete photocopy of commerical songbook Origin:; genreform: Commercial Songbook (Box 10)
      Songbook -- Commercial
    - Campfire Songs, 1994; 1 copy; Notes: Small format paperback, squarebound, glossy cover. ISBN 1-56440-372-6, second edition, third printing Origin: The Globe Pequot Press; genreform: Commercial Songbook (Box 13)
    - Christmas for the Guitar, 1972; Karamar Pub Co. LTD; 1 copy; Notes: Bonus pull out coloring section Origin: Karamar Pub Co. LTD, 1972; genreform: Commercial Songbook (Box 10)
    - Colonial & Revolution Songbook with Historical Commentary, 1996; 1 copy; Notes: White staple bound ISBN 1-878360-08-6, companion to the recording of the same name. Origin: WEM Records; genreform: Commercial Songbook (Box 13)
    - Concert Hour, 1960; Handy-Folio Music Co, 1960; 1 copy; Notes: Instruction book for Symphonet Origin: Handy-Folio Music Co, 1960; genreform: Commercial Songbook (Box 10)
    - Down to Earth: Love Songs, 1984; 1 copy; Notes: Blue cover, pamphlet style, staple bound Origin:; genreform: Commercial Songbook (Box 14)
    - Folksinger's Wordbook, Deluxe Edition, 1973; Oak Publications, 1973; 1 copy; Notes: Spiral bound, red cover Origin: Oak Publications, 1973; genreform: Commercial Songbook (Box 10)
    - Great Songs of the Sixties 2, 1974; 1 copy; Notes: Square bound Origin: Quradrangle/The New York Times Book Co.; genreform: Commercial Songbook (Box 13)
    - Harmony Baroque to Contemporary, Part 1, 1991; 1 copy; Notes: Square bound. second printing ISBN 0-87563-373-0 Origin: Stipes Publishing Company; genreform: Commercial Songbook (Box 13)
    - Harmony Hour, 1960; Handy-Folio Music Co, 1960; 1 copy; Notes: Instruction book for Soprano flute Origin: Handy-Folio Music Co, 1960; genreform: Commercial Songbook (Box 10)
    - Jay Arnold's Easy to Play Guitar Chords, 1964; 1 copy; Notes: In very delicate shape. All pages have come away from spine. Pages are still stapled together. Origin: Charles Hanson Music and Books; genreform: Commercial Songbook (Box 13)
    - Music Language & Fundamentals, 1994; 1 copy; Notes: Square bound, three hole punched, second edition, ISBN 0-697-12497-5 Origin: W.C.B. Brown & Benchmark; genreform: Commercial Songbook (Box 13)
    - September 11th, 2001: A Memorial Songbook, 1 copy; Notes: Blue cover with world trade center Origin: M.A.S.S.F.I.L.C.; genreform: Commercial Songbook (Box 16)
    - SightSinging 4th Edition, Complete, 1986; 1 copy; Notes: Commercial songbook, Benward, Bruce Origin: 1986 edition; genreform: Commercial Songbook (Box 10)
    - The Complete Phil Ochs, 1978; 1 copy; Notes: Square bound, photo coverISBN 0-897-05010-x Origin: Almo Publications; genreform: Commercial Songbook (Box 13)
    - Heather Alexander's Complete Song Book, original lyrics and music, 15 August 2007; 1 copy; Notes: Firebird emblem on cream cover, spiral bound. Signed to Harold in thanks. Signature is unreadable but is probably Alexander James Adams Origin: Sea Fire Productions, Inc.; genreform: Songbook (Box 16)
      Songbook
    - The Guitar with Frederick Node, 1982; 1 copy; Notes: Staple bound paperback, could be a tie in with a TV show from LA school district Origin: KLCSTB 58; genreform: Commercial Songbook (Box 13)
    - The Judy Collins Songbook, 12th printing, 1977; Collins, Judy; Grosset & Dunlap, 1977; 1 copy; Notes: Square bound with artist's face on cover Origin: Grosset & Dunlap, 1977; genreform: Commercial Songbook (Box 10)
    - The Mad Scientist's Songbook, 1998; 1 copy; Notes: Yellow cover with mad scientist at keyboard, spiral bound Origin: Published by M.A.S.S.F.I.L.C.; genreform: Commercial Songbook (Box 14)
    - The War Is Over: Phil Ochs, 1968; 1 copy; Notes: Torn cover Origin: Barricade Music, Inc.; genreform: Commercial Songbook (Box 13)
    - Two-Tune Harmony Songs for Symphonet, Voice or Melody Chimes, 1960; 1 copy; Notes: Pamphlet style, grey scale cover Origin: Handy-Folio Music Co.; genreform: Commercial Songbook (Box 13)
    - Your Friendly Neighborhood Magician, 2006; 1 copy; Notes: Signed, pamphlet format, chapbook, staple bound, limited edition, #100 copies Origin: Tachyon Publications; genreform: Commercial Songbook (Box 16)
    - Chainik Press Publications
      - Rivets Redux: A science fiction musical presented by Boskone 15 and the RISFA Players, 1978; Chainik Press Publications; 2 copy; Notes: Beige book, stapled Origin: Chainik Press Publications, Publication #68, 1978 in-print (different version/edition): http://data.nesfa.org/press/Books/KellerAnderson.html (Box 10, Box 16)
        Musical; Songbook; Convention -- Boskone 15
      - Mik Ado About Nothing (Back to Rivets, part 1), Second edition, 1 August 1980; 1 copy; Notes: Limited edition of 250 copies. Blue cover with Cthulu in beanie with ProCon 1980 on forehead, holding a lobster Origin: Chainik Press Publications in-print (different version/edition): http://data.nesfa.org/press/Books/KellerAnderson.html (Box 16)
        Musical; Songbook; Convention -- Boskone 14
    - Leslie Fish